jse.co.za 2012-05-24

# JSE Limited - Privacy Policy

The JSE takes the privacy of its users seriously. The JSE is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users while providing a personalised and valuable service. The JSE’s privacy policy, which forms part of the Website terms of use, explains the data processing practices of the JSE in so far as it relates to the www.jse.co.za website (the “ **Website** ”). The JSE has reasonable security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and interception by third parties of the information under our control, but, to the extent allowed by law, the JSE assumes no liability for any loss or damages you or anyone else may suffer as a result of interception, alteration or misuse of information transmitted over the Internet.

The above wording limits and excludes obligations, liabilities and legal responsibilities of the JSE, and also limits and excludes your rights and remedies and places various risks, liabilities, obligations and legal responsibilities on you.

By using the Website, you are consenting to this privacy policy and the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by the JSE as outlined in this privacy policy. If this privacy policy is not acceptable to you, please do not submit any of your personal information. 

If you have any request concerning your personal information, wish to make any amendment to your personal information or have any queries with regard to these practices please contact us by sending an email to [**webadmin@jse.co.za**](mailto:webadmin@jse.co.za). 

If we make any changes to this privacy policy, we will post them on this page.

## Information collected

We may choose to collect personal information from you via the Website through the use of enquiry and registration forms and every time you e-mail us your details.

## Use and disclosure of personal information

We may process personal information collected via the Website for the purposes of –

  * conducting market consultation exercises; or 
  * providing you with information about new developments on or any changes to the services provided via the Website 

If you do not wish to receive information about our products or services, please indicate this in the appropriate box when providing us with your details (if applicable to this Website).

We may also use information in aggregate form (so that no individual user is identified) to –

  * build up marketing profiles 
  * aid strategic development; 
  * manage our relationship with advertisers; and 
  * audit usage of the Website. 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties where:

  * we have your consent; 
  * we use third parties to assist us in providing services and you have elected to receive one of those services. The third party would only be allowed to use your information for the purposes of providing that service to you; or 
  * we are compelled by law or a court order to do so, or if we believe that such action is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interest pursued by the JSE, to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of the JSE, the Website, visitors to the Website or others. 

## Law enforcement authorities

We may, in our discretion, contact law enforcement authorities if we believe that anything unlawful is occurring in connection with the Website. In this process, we may provide the law enforcement authorities with any personal data that is held by us. 

## Use of cookies

Cookies may be placed on your computer when you both visit and register on the Website. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information back from the browser. Find out more about the use of cookies on [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/). 

The JSE may use cookies to identify you when you access the Website and to build up a demographic profile. The use of cookies also allows registered users to be presented with a personalised version of the Website.

By your use of the Website you agree that the JSE may use cookies. 

Please ensure that you read the Website terms of use  as well.
